Guide to the George Mason University Office of the President records, 1949-2004
George Mason University Libraries
- Series 6: George W. Johnson, 1957-2004, (78 boxes)
  - Report on statewide financial management and compliance, 1994-1997 (Box 86, Folder 9)
  - Request for proposals for the Northern Virginia Graduate Center (Joint committee), 1993 (Box 86, Folder 10)
  - GMU response to Commission on Colleges, 1991 (Box 86, Folder 11)
  - Revision of adminiatrative procedure 12, March 17, 1992 (Box 86, Folder 12)
  - Richard Anderson vs. Radford University, 1988 (Box 86, Folder 13)
  - "The role of the college or university president in institutional advancement" by John Michael Slinker, September 1988 (Box 86, Folder 14)
  - Safeguarding of payroll checks, 1978 (Box 87, Folder 1)
  - School of Information Technology and Engineering, Fall 1990 (Box 87, Folder 2)
  - George Johnson scrapbook (Photographs), 1980s (Box 87, Folder 3)
  - George Johnson scrapbook (Photographs), 1980s (Box 87, Folder 4)
  - George Johnson scrapbook (Photographs), 1980s (Box 87, Folder 5)
  - Secretary of Education: Speeches, 1990-1998 (Box 87, Folder 6)
  - Secretary of Finance, 1991-1993 (Box 87, Folder 7)
  - Sexual assault: "Sexual assault on campus", 1988 (Box 87, Folder 8)
  - Sexual assault policy, September 4, 1992 (Box 87, Folder 9)
  - Sexual assault task force, 1991-1992 (Box 87, Folder 10)
  - Sexual assault task force final report, June 3, 1993 (Box 87, Folder 11)
  - Sexual harrassment board, 1994 (Box 87, Folder 12)
  - Sexual harrassment policy and procedures, 1993-1994 (Box 87, Folder 13)
  - Sigma Chi incident, 1991 (Box 87, Folder 14)
  - Signature authorizations by the president, 1987, 1989 (Box 87, Folder 15)
  - Signature authorizations by the president, 1991-1992 (Box 87, Folder 16)
  - Signature authorizations by the president, 1993-1994 (Box 87, Folder 17)
  - Signature authorizations by the president, 1995-1996 (Box 87, Folder 18)
  - Southern Association of Colleges and Schools (SACS) self-study (1 of 2), 1990-1991 (Box 88, Folder 1)
  - Southern Association of Colleges and Schools (SACS) self-study (2 of 2), 1990-1991 (Box 88, Folder 2)
  - Southeastern Universities Research Association, 1992-1998 (Box 88, Folder 3)
  - Special file, 1996 (Box 88, Folder 4)
  - Speeches (1978-1996) (Box 88, Folder 5)
  - George W. Johnson speech: Authority and continuity in liberal arts, circa 1978 (Box 88, Folder 6)
  - George W. Johnson speech: Speech to area III principal, August 7, 1978 (Box 88, Folder 7)
  - George W. Johnson speech: Staff meeting, September 1978 (Box 88, Folder 8)
  - George W. Johnson speech: SCHEV (State Council of Higher Education Virginia), December 1978 (Box 88, Folder 9)
  - George W. Johnson speech: Address to SCHEV (State Council of Higher Education Virginia), December 4, 1978 (Box 88, Folder 10)
  - George W. Johnson speech: Legislative breakfast, December 15, 1978 (Box 88, Folder 11)
  - George W. Johnson speech: Interim report on 1978-1979 prospectus for 1979-1980, circa 1979 (Box 88, Folder 12)
  - George W. Johnson speech: Address to board of supervisors, circa 1979 (Box 88, Folder 13)
  - George W. Johnson speech: Members of Law School committee, circa 1979 (Box 88, Folder 14)
  - George W. Johnson speech: Address to Virginia society of professional engineers, February 24, 1979 (Box 88, Folder 15)
  - George W. Johnson speech: Fairfax County Chamber of Commerce, July 2, 1979 (Box 88, Folder 16)
  - George W. Johnson speech: University update, July 12, 1979 (Box 88, Folder 17)
  - George W. Johnson speech: Comments for summer commencement, August 4, 1979 (Box 88, Folder 18)
  - George W. Johnson speech: General faculty meeting address, September 5, 1979 (Box 88, Folder 19)
  - George W. Johnson speech: Fairfax County Chamber of Commerce, September 21, 1979 (Box 88, Folder 20)
  - George W. Johnson speech: Joint NVCC/GMU legislative dinner, November 29, 1979 (Box 88, Folder 21)
  - George W. Johnson speech: FAC senate, December 4, 1979 (Box 88, Folder 22)
  - George W. Johnson speech: The larger dimensions, December 9, 1979 (Box 88, Folder 23)
  - George W. Johnson speech: Kiwanis, circa 1980 (Box 88, Folder 24)
  - George W. Johnson speech: Patriot kick-off dinner, circa 1980 (Box 88, Folder 25)
  - George W. Johnson speech: The comptroller/the commissar, January 23, 1980 (Box 88, Folder 26)
  - George W. Johnson speech: Faculty senate, February 1980 (Box 88, Folder 27)
  - George W. Johnson speech: The age of distrust, BDM corporation, February 22, 1980 (Box 88, Folder 28)
  - George W. Johnson speech: Faculty senate, March 19, 1980 (Box 88, Folder 29)
  - George W. Johnson speech: First annual University Day, April 7, 1980 (Box 88, Folder 30)
  - George W. Johnson speech: Founders Day, Clinch Valley College, April 9, 1980 (Box 88, Folder 31)
  - George W. Johnson speech: Fairfax City Chamber of Commerce, June 26, 1980 (Box 88, Folder 32)
  - George W. Johnson speech: University update, July 1, 1980 (Box 88, Folder 33)
  - George W. Johnson speech: GMU forum on energy, July 9, 1980 (Box 88, Folder 34)
  - George W. Johnson speech: Law School dedication, graduation script, August 23, 1980 (Box 88, Folder 35)
  - George W. Johnson speech: Interim report on progress in 1979-1980, prospectus for 1980-1981, August 27, 1980 (Box 88, Folder 36)
  - George W. Johnson speech: Board report, September 10, 1980 (Box 88, Folder 37)
  - George W. Johnson speech: State of the University message, September 17, 1980 (Box 88, Folder 38)
  - George W. Johnson speech: President's board, Board of Visitors (BOV) meeting, November 12, 1980 (Box 88, Folder 39)
  - George W. Johnson speech: Presentation to State Council of Higher Education (SCHEV), January 6, 1981 (Box 88, Folder 40)
  - George W. Johnson speech: President's report, January 14, 1981 (Box 88, Folder 41)
  - George W. Johnson speech: Legislative tour, welcoming remarks, January 31, 1981 (Box 88, Folder 42)
  - George W. Johnson speech: Program budget, meeting with Gilley, March 11, 1981 (Box 88, Folder 43)
  - George W. Johnson speech: Convocation script, April 7, 1981 (Box 88, Folder 44)
  - George W. Johnson speech: Groundbreaking script, April 7, 1981 (Box 88, Folder 45)
  - George W. Johnson speech: Virginia's investment in higher education in the 1980s, April 16, 1981 (Box 89, Folder 1)
  - George W. Johnson speech: Introduction for Helen Hill Miller, May 7, 1981 (Box 89, Folder 2)
  - George W. Johnson speech: Commencement, welcome address, May 16, 1981 (Box 89, Folder 3)
  - George W. Johnson speech: Board of Visitors (BOV) annual meeting, August 1981 (Box 89, Folder 4)
  - George W. Johnson speech: Notes on President's retreat, September 1981 (Box 89, Folder 5)
  - George W. Johnson speech: Talk to DW staff, September 2, 1981 (Box 89, Folder 6)
  - George W. Johnson speech: State of the University address, September 10, 1981 (Box 89, Folder 7)
  - George W. Johnson speech: No title, September 16, 1981 (Box 89, Folder 8)
  - George W. Johnson speech: ATT, September 17, 1981 (Box 89, Folder 9)
  - George W. Johnson speech: Testimony, October 26, 1981 (Box 89, Folder 10)
  - George W. Johnson speech: Notes for board orientation, November 1981 (Box 89, Folder 11)
  - George W. Johnson speech: Notes for Board of Visitors (BOV) meeting, November 11, 1981 (Box 89, Folder 12)
  - George W. Johnson speech: Presentation to board of supervisors, November 16, 1981 (Box 89, Folder 13)
  - George W. Johnson speech: Introductory statement for legislative dinner, December 1981 (Box 89, Folder 14)
  - George W. Johnson speech: State Council for Higher Education (SCHEV), December 15, 1981 (Box 89, Folder 15)
  - George W. Johnson speech: Commencement address, East Tennessee State University, December 18, 1981 (Box 89, Folder 16)
  - George W. Johnson speech: Virginia Independent Schools Association, state wrestling tournament, circa 1982 (Box 89, Folder 17)
  - George W. Johnson speech: Board of Visitors (BOV), January 12, 1982 (Box 89, Folder 18)
  - George W. Johnson speech: Board of Visitors (BOV) assessment and budget, January 26, 1982 (Box 89, Folder 19)
  - George W. Johnson speech: Meeting with Governor, February 1, 1982 (Box 89, Folder 20)
  - George W. Johnson speech: Capital outlay subcommittee, February 9, 1982 (Box 89, Folder 21)
  - George W. Johnson speech: Senate finance committee meeting, March 1, 1982 (Box 89, Folder 22)
  - George W. Johnson speech: Board of Visitors (BOV), March 10, 1982 (Box 89, Folder 23)
  - George W. Johnson speech: Address to the general faculty, March 31, 1982 (Box 89, Folder 24)
  - George W. Johnson speech: Greetings for University Day convocation, April 7, 1982 (Box 89, Folder 25)
  - George W. Johnson speech: Testimony for hearings, establishment of a National Academy of Peace, April 21, 1982 (Box 89, Folder 26)
  - George W. Johnson speech: Board of Visitors (BOV), May 12, 1982 (Box 89, Folder 27)
  - George W. Johnson speech: Commencement speech, May 22, 1982 (Box 89, Folder 28)
  - George W. Johnson speech: Chamber of Commerce luncheon address, June 24, 1982 (Box 89, Folder 29)
  - George W. Johnson speech: State of the University message, September 15, 1982 (Box 89, Folder 30)
  - George W. Johnson speech: Report to Board of Visitors (BOV) finance committee, September 22, 1982 (Box 89, Folder 31)
  - George W. Johnson speech: Report to Board of Visitors (BOV), September 22, 1982 (Box 89, Folder 32)
  - George W. Johnson speech: Dedication of campus station, October 27, 1982 (Box 89, Folder 33)
  - George W. Johnson speech: Enrollment growth, November 5, 1982 (Box 89, Folder 34)
  - George W. Johnson speech: Board of Visitors (BOV), November 8, 1982 (Box 89, Folder 35)
  - George W. Johnson speech: No title, November 10, 1982 (Box 89, Folder 36)
  - George W. Johnson speech: Politics of higher education, November 19, 1982 (Box 89, Folder 37)
  - George W. Johnson speech: American education: The continuing success story, November 20, 1982 (Box 89, Folder 38)
  - George W. Johnson speech: Legislative dinner, December 8, 1982 (Box 89, Folder 39)
  - George W. Johnson speech: AASCU (American Association of State Colleges and Universities) summer meeting, circa 1983 (Box 89, Folder 40)
  - George W. Johnson speech: Biennium report, circa 1983 (Box 89, Folder 41)
  - George W. Johnson speech: Education for economic development, 1983 (Box 89, Folder 42)
  - George W. Johnson speech: Assessment report, January 31, 1983 (Box 89, Folder 43)
  - George W. Johnson speech: Til Hazel turkey roast, February 1983 (Box 89, Folder 44)
  - George W. Johnson speech: On behalf of AASCU (American Association of State Colleges and Universities), February 1983 (Box 89, Folder 45)
  - George W. Johnson speech: Law School faculty luncheon, March 23, 1983 (Box 89, Folder 46)
  - George W. Johnson speech: Address to general faculty, March 30, 1983 (Box 89, Folder 47)
  - George W. Johnson speech: Urban university and economic development, March 30, 1983 (Box 89, Folder 48)
  - George W. Johnson speech: Alumni board, April 2, 1983 (Box 89, Folder 49)
  - George W. Johnson speech: Board of visitors (BOV), May 9, 1983 (Box 89, Folder 50)
  - George W. Johnson speech: Board of visitors (BOV), May 10, 1983 (Box 89, Folder 51)
  - George W. Johnson speech: St. Stephen's commencement speech, June 11, 1983 (Box 89, Folder 52)
  - George W. Johnson speech: What an English professor has learned, August 12, 1983 (Box 89, Folder 53)
  - George W. Johnson speech: Board of visitors (BOV), September 1983 (Box 89, Folder 54)
  - George W. Johnson speech: Vienne administration council, September 13, 1983 (Box 89, Folder 55)
  - George W. Johnson speech: Board of visitors (BOV), September 14, 1983 (Box 89, Folder 56)
  - George W. Johnson speech: Federation, September 14, 1983 (Box 89, Folder 57)
  - George W. Johnson speech: State of the University, September 21, 1983 (Box 89, Folder 58)
  - George W. Johnson speech: Cybernatics conference presentation, October 7, 1983 (Box 89, Folder 59)
  - George W. Johnson speech: Board of Visitors (BOV), November 9, 1983 (Box 89, Folder 60)
  - George W. Johnson speech: Governor's conference, November 29, 1983 (Box 89, Folder 61)
  - George W. Johnson speech: On behalf of AASCU (American Association of State Colleges and Universities), 1984 (Box 89, Folder 62)
  - George W. Johnson speech: Senate, January 1984 (Box 89, Folder 63)
  - George W. Johnson speech: Rotary Israel, January 1984 (Box 89, Folder 64)
  - George W. Johnson speech: GMI press conference, January 30, 1984 (Box 89, Folder 65)
  - George W. Johnson speech: Capital outlay hearing, February 3, 1984 (Box 89, Folder 66)
  - George W. Johnson speech: Senate finances, February 16, 1984 (Box 89, Folder 67)
  - George W. Johnson speech: FND, long-range planning committee, March 20, 1984 (Box 89, Folder 68)
  - George W. Johnson speech: Accounts, March 21, 1984 (Box 89, Folder 69)
  - George W. Johnson speech: Speech to the general faculty, March 28, 1984 (Box 89, Folder 70)
  - George W. Johnson speech: Student forum, March 30, 1984 (Box 90, Folder 1)
  - George W. Johnson speech: Introduction for Father J. Hehir, April 5, 1984 (Box 90, Folder 2)
  - George W. Johnson speech: Faculty honors assembly welcome, April 6, 1984 (Box 90, Folder 3)
  - George W. Johnson speech: High tech symposium, April 10, 1984 (Box 90, Folder 4)
  - George W. Johnson speech: American Academy of Sciences, April 10, 1984 (Box 90, Folder 5)
  - George W. Johnson speech: Business and education in Northern Virginia, April 17, 1984 (Box 90, Folder 6)
  - George W. Johnson speech: Board of Visitors (BOV), May 16, 1984 (Box 90, Folder 7)
  - George W. Johnson speech: Fairfax committee of 100, June 30, 1984 (Box 90, Folder 8)
  - George W. Johnson speech: Board of Visitors (BOV), September 12, 1984 (Box 90, Folder 9)
  - George W. Johnson speech: General faculty address, September 19, 1984 (Box 90, Folder 10)
  - George W. Johnson speech: Chamber of Commerce tour, September 26, 1984 (Box 90, Folder 11)
  - George W. Johnson speech: Senate finance committee, September 27, 1984 (Box 90, Folder 12)
  - George W. Johnson speech: Manassas Chamber of Commerce seminar, October 2, 1984 (Box 90, Folder 13)
  - George W. Johnson speech: State of the University speech to students, October 4, 1984 (Box 90, Folder 14)
  - George W. Johnson speech: AASCU (American Association of State Colleges and Universities) "New Presidents", November 15, 1984 (Box 90, Folder 15)
  - George W. Johnson speech: Year of the College, November 27, 1984 (Box 90, Folder 16)
  - George W. Johnson speech: Legislative dinner notes, December 5, 1984 (Box 90, Folder 17)
  - George W. Johnson speech: Full board meeting, Janaury 9, 1985 (Box 90, Folder 18)
  - George W. Johnson speech: Continuing education presentation, University of Maryland, February 7, 1985 (Box 90, Folder 19)
  - George W. Johnson speech: Board of Trade, PAC, March 1985 (Box 90, Folder 20)
  - George W. Johnson speech: Robinson professors, March 1985 (Box 90, Folder 21)
  - George W. Johnson speech: AASCU (American Association of State Colleges and Universities), March 11, 1985 (Box 90, Folder 22)
  - George W. Johnson speech: Board of Visitors (BOV) report, March 19, 1985 (Box 90, Folder 23)
  - George W. Johnson speech: Speech to general faculty, April 17, 1985 (Box 90, Folder 24)
  - George W. Johnson speech: Board of Visitors (BOV) report, May 8, 1985 (Box 90, Folder 25)
  - George W. Johnson speech: Capital outlay tour, May 22, 1985 (Box 90, Folder 26)
  - George W. Johnson speech: Capital outlay presentation, July 23, 1985 (Box 90, Folder 27)
  - George W. Johnson speech: Goals of the SBA 1984-1989, August 1985 (Box 90, Folder 28)
  - George W. Johnson speech: Arlington school administration, August 13, 1985 (Box 90, Folder 29)
  - George W. Johnson speech: Bar Association, September 17, 1985 (Box 90, Folder 30)
  - George W. Johnson speech: Faculty address, September 18, 1985 (Box 90, Folder 31)
  - George W. Johnson speech: Roanoke speech, September 20, 1985 (Box 90, Folder 32)
  - George W. Johnson speech: State Council for Higher Education (SCHEV) nursing appeal, October 2, 1985 (Box 90, Folder 33)
  - George W. Johnson speech: Material for President Johnson, October 3, 1985 (Box 90, Folder 34)
  - George W. Johnson speech: Committee on self-regulation, October 15, 1985 (Box 90, Folder 35)
  - George W. Johnson speech: Chamber roads meeting, October 28, 1985 (Box 90, Folder 36)
  - George W. Johnson speech: Foundation, October 28, 1985 (Box 90, Folder 37)
  - George W. Johnson speech: Lord Fairfax Community College, October 31, 1985 (Box 90, Folder 38)
  - George W. Johnson speech: Legislative dinner, December 5, 1985 (Box 90, Folder 39)
  - George W. Johnson speech: Dedication of George Mason University, circa 1986 (Box 90, Folder 40)
  - George W. Johnson speech: Faculty salary enhancement, circa 1986 (Box 90, Folder 41)
  - George W. Johnson speech: American Jewish committee, January 14, 1986 (Box 90, Folder 42)
  - George W. Johnson speech: Remarks to the State Council of Higher Education (SCHEV) on behalf of Council of Presidents, February 5, 1986 (Box 90, Folder 43)
  - George W. Johnson speech: Articles and notes, February 19, 1986 (Box 90, Folder 44)
  - George W. Johnson speech: Art's council, February 20, 1986 (Box 90, Folder 45)
  - George W. Johnson speech: National Association of College/Universities Attorney's, February 28, 1986 (Box 90, Folder 46)
  - George W. Johnson speech: President's council, March 19, 1986 (Box 90, Folder 47)
  - George W. Johnson speech: Desperate things (Elizabeth Town inaugural), April 5, 1986 (Box 90, Folder 48)
  - George W. Johnson speech: University Day, April 7, 1986 (Box 90, Folder 49)
  - George W. Johnson speech: Attorneys speech New Orleans, April 18, 1986 (Box 90, Folder 50)
  - George W. Johnson speech: Report to general faculty, April 30, 1986 (Box 90, Folder 51)
  - George W. Johnson speech: Coleman Raphael breakfast, May 14, 1986 (Box 90, Folder 52)
  - George W. Johnson speech: Commencement, May 17, 1986 (Box 90, Folder 53)
  - George W. Johnson speech: Time capsule, June 5, 1986 (Box 90, Folder 54)
  - George W. Johnson speech: Business leaders, July 1986 (Box 90, Folder 55)
  - George W. Johnson speech: Business leadership, July 15, 1986 (Box 90, Folder 56)
  - George W. Johnson speech: GMU development strategy, August 1986 (Box 90, Folder 57)
  - George W. Johnson speech: No title, September 14, 1986 (Box 90, Folder 58)
  - George W. Johnson speech: Dean's meeting, September 15, 1986 (Box 90, Folder 59)
  - George W. Johnson speech: State of the University speech, September 17, 1986 (Box 90, Folder 60)
  - George W. Johnson speech: GMI, September 22, 1986 (Box 90, Folder 61)
  - George W. Johnson speech: AGB speech (Academic affair mini conference, University of Oklahoma), October 2, 1986 (Box 90, Folder 62)
  - George W. Johnson speech: Legislative staff briefing, November 6, 1986 (Box 90, Folder 63)
  - George W. Johnson speech: Slide show: Bennett, Covey, November 6, 1986 (Box 91, Folder 1)
  - George W. Johnson speech: Presentation to Ad Hoc salary review group, November 19, 1986 (Box 91, Folder 2)
  - George W. Johnson speech: Earl Dickinson visit, December 1, 1986 (Box 91, Folder 3)
  - George W. Johnson speech: Legislative dinner, December 3, 1986 (Box 91, Folder 4)
  - George W. Johnson speech: Leadership, University development, circa 1987 (Box 91, Folder 5)
  - George W. Johnson speech: Harvard Business School club, 1987 (Box 91, Folder 6)
  - George W. Johnson speech: Legislative dinner, 1987 (Box 91, Folder 7)
  - George W. Johnson speech: GMU development strategy, January 1987 (Box 91, Folder 8)
  - George W. Johnson speech: Enrollment management, January 16, 1987 (Box 91, Folder 9)
  - George W. Johnson speech: Dean's meeting, January 17, 1987 (Box 91, Folder 10)
  - George W. Johnson speech: HBG, February 10, 1987 (Box 91, Folder 11)
  - George W. Johnson speech: Presentation to University Coordination Group, February 16, 1987 (Box 91, Folder 12)
  - George W. Johnson speech: Report to Board of Visitors (BOV) executive committee meeting, March 4, 1987 (Box 91, Folder 13)
  - George W. Johnson speech: AGB speech (New Orleans), March 23, 1987 (Box 91, Folder 14)
  - George W. Johnson speech: Response to turkey roast, April 11, 1987 (Box 91, Folder 15)
  - George W. Johnson speech: No title (delivered by Dr. Gazale), April 15, 1987 (Box 91, Folder 16)
  - George W. Johnson speech: Meeting with McDiarmid, April 28, 1987 (Box 91, Folder 17)
  - George W. Johnson speech: Statement of University's game plan, May 6, 1987 (Box 91, Folder 18)
  - George W. Johnson speech: Dean's meeting, May 6, 1987 (Box 91, Folder 19)
  - George W. Johnson speech: ACB, May 14, 1987 (Box 91, Folder 20)
  - George W. Johnson speech: Twentieth spring commencement, May 16, 1987 (Box 91, Folder 21)
  - George W. Johnson speech: Joint finance committee, GA assembly, June 1, 1987 (Box 91, Folder 22)
  - George W. Johnson speech: Higher education business/industry, June 4, 1987 (Box 91, Folder 23)
  - George W. Johnson speech: Richmond dinner, June 22, 1987 (Box 91, Folder 24)
  - George W. Johnson speech: Manassas Chamber of Commerce, June 25, 1987 (Box 91, Folder 25)
  - George W. Johnson speech: SCUP (Society for College and University Planning), July 21, 1987 (Box 91, Folder 26)
  - George W. Johnson speech: T and D, July 22, 1987 (Box 91, Folder 27)
  - George W. Johnson speech: Statement of GMU's game plan, September 1987 (Box 91, Folder 28)
  - George W. Johnson speech: State Council of Higher Education (SCHEV), September 2, 1987 (Box 91, Folder 29)
  - George W. Johnson speech: Capital outlay slide show, September 9, 1987 (Box 91, Folder 30)
  - George W. Johnson speech: Kiwanni Manassas, September 10, 1987 (Box 91, Folder 31)
  - George W. Johnson speech: Presidents work of the year, Board of Visitors (BOV), September 15, 1987 (Box 91, Folder 32)
  - George W. Johnson speech: Arts and humanities reception, September 15, 1987 (Box 91, Folder 33)
  - George W. Johnson speech: Faculty address, September 15, 1987 (Box 91, Folder 34)
  - George W. Johnson speech: General faculty speech, September 16, 1987 (Box 91, Folder 35)
  - George W. Johnson speech: Arlington economic development, October 9, 1982 (Box 91, Folder 36)
  - George W. Johnson speech: NoVA roundtable, October 19, 1987 (Box 91, Folder 37)
  - George W. Johnson speech: CC advisory board, Roanoke, November 5, 1987 (Box 91, Folder 38)
  - George W. Johnson speech: Black student leadership conference, November 6, 1987 (Box 91, Folder 39)
  - George W. Johnson speech: Women in academe, November 7, 1987 (Box 91, Folder 40)
  - George W. Johnson speech: Guest editorial for Business Outlook, November 8, 1987 (Box 91, Folder 41)
  - George W. Johnson speech: GMI, December 14, 1987 (Box 91, Folder 42)
  - George W. Johnson speech: Winchester Rotary, circa 1988 (Box 91, Folder 43)
  - George W. Johnson speech: Martin Luther King celebration, January 25, 1988 (Box 91, Folder 44)
  - George W. Johnson speech: Manassas Chamber of Commerce, January 26, 1988 (Box 91, Folder 45)
  - George W. Johnson speech: Manuscript chapter, the President's game, March 1988 (Box 91, Folder 46)
  - George W. Johnson speech: Report to faculty, academic standards committee, March 14, 1988 (Box 91, Folder 47)
  - George W. Johnson speech: No title, March 14, 1988 (Box 91, Folder 48)
  - George W. Johnson speech: Dedication, April 7, 1988 (Box 91, Folder 49)
  - George W. Johnson speech: Alexandria rotary, April 12, 1988 (Box 91, Folder 50)
  - George W. Johnson speech: Student leadership dinner, April 26, 1988 (Box 91, Folder 51)
  - George W. Johnson speech: General faculty meeting, April 27, 1988 (Box 91, Folder 52)